Welcome to A Notion South Edition.
Friends, in today's video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard jobs
and apart from this, friends,
we will talk about other companies where you will find the
job of a product manager and how to
play that job
and how to perform it.
We will tell you complete information about it.
Before returning, I request you
that if you have not subscribed to the study channel, then please
subscribe.
But please press subscribe so that you can pay attention to
whose job notifications reach you first. So
first of all let's talk
about the number job here
and we will talk about it one more time.
Secondly, you will also get the job of an acid product manager here, it will be
absolutely free of cost. Okay, so if you want to apply for a
room butt job, then here
you will get the job of unit sales manager,
and here
you can clearly see the interview process. You can
apply for any candidate up to seven years old, but
secondly, here you  The age limit
given here is that you should be at least above 20 years or
within twenty years, this should be okay and the
salary is also very good friends,
if
you think turmeric is on the basis of your interview performance, it can be more, there are
200 interviews here or leaders can
come online sitting at home,
they can also see Hindus and I will
tell you that the second location that has been permitted here is
in Hyderabad, Bangalore and Mumbai exam and secondly
friends, the product manager, such
product will be made in the place all over India,
Tulsi or we will talk to you about one here
which ICC attracts, so
here I have given you two more phone numbers and so
friends, if you want, you can
WhatsApp your resume here, then
you can meet them, okay, when
done, we will send a Zoom email, do it sitting at home,
your exit quote will be done, if you
send it in average, he will get a call back and that is, if you
call the person, if you want to talk, he will automatically give
you the information  You can also take it now, let's go
here, let's talk
about the skin job which is Asset Product
Manager's answer, that the lever tap company
is landing, you are going to go secondly, you will
press the railway, next Mica platform,
here you will get to see the jobs,
through this platform friends only
you will get this job and here you will get Durg,
so let me tell you how to get it, then we will
talk further, here the Asset Product
Manager is the second, here first of all we
talk about the salary, so by
taking a breath here you can get up to one lakh rupees, along with
this, on the
other hand, we bring jobs here
which are from Sharp Cost Quora company
and this is the second here you will have a
job of research and development, okay now if you
want to add sugar in it, then
I have given its registered link here,
go and open it, open it, click on the
question, click on the test, a
page will open in front of you, enter
your mobile number and your
education qualification and submit it,
after that see here only
in this such product  Apart from judgment,
ask about the test because
in this platform I keep making a lot of videos,
so all the candidates who have been
rated, okay, you have been
rated a lot through this platform and you
can also get straightened out as I am telling you,
after resting, you can take out
whatever proper test you want to do here,
after that
you have some support here, go here and check
out how to give this test, so
before giving the test here, you
can do free practice here, okay,
you will get many options here in practice,
take practical and one more special thing will come here, so
before this, this test was for
100 marks out of 100, but now it has been made
clear that out of 100, you have to
score only 151 on the basis, okay, so
here you are asked for a face mask out of 1000, then
you will get pimples here
and if you get pimples, friends, let me
tell you, here you are
in the related  If you check, you will see
that the other students who are cancer,
this hinge here is absolutely fine, so today you need to
register by clicking on the strip test,
if you come in their achievers board
or you come and bring it, then
here you are also
given a moment's goddess from the company's platform, Incredible,
as if it will be given to you as a gift, there will be no
cost for it, you will get the option
here, this network iWatch for that